I'm going to freestyle and make you fall in love with me!
Okay!
Yakan-kun, I'm looking forward to working with you today.
We're going to test your ad-lib skills.
Let's start with this.
You're the class president. You find a student slacking off on cleaning and you warn him.
You tell him you love him for cleaning up.
Oh!
Yes, I understand.
Boys, you've got to clean up.
Don't do it like this.
Don't ride on the broom.
Don't play fight. Sweep properly.
Sweep it up.
Hey!
You listen to me, don't you?
You're so obedient.
Hmm.
That's what I like about you.
I kind of like it.
Because you said it.
Hey, cleaning up.
Am I right?
Uhh! Hee-hee-hee.
Yes!
Stage one clear!
Please!
Make it easy!
Oh!
I think I got it!
Fireworks night
From high above the city.
While you're watching the fireworks, just the two of you.
I'm gonna tell him I love him.
Isn't it perfect for the season?
Let's go.
It's so beautiful, isn't it?
You can see them from here.
Bamaya!
Whew!
I love it!
Fireworks.
I love fireworks.
Oh, no.
It's you.
Tere!
That's not good.
But I'm...
I'm planning to tell her I like her.
I want to be told that I like you.
I want you to tell me that you like me.
This is the last one.
Okay.
This one's a little bit... sticky?
You're in a haunted house and you don't like being scared.
You're about to cry and tell him you love him.
Wait...
You're going to tell her in a haunted house?
Can't we tell her after we get out?
Do we have to tell him inside?Do I have to tell them inside?
Okay.
Oh, no!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I really, really, really can't. I really, really can't do this.
Can I hold your hand?
I'm scared.
But I'm glad we're holding hands.
Can we hold hands after we leave?
I like that.
No! Get out of here!
Poki-san ne Operator background
This uses a lot of energy.
Thank you very much.
I've never said I love you so much.
But once in a while, I think I have to do something like this.
I'm an idol.
It doesn't happen often with orcas.
Orcas are in charge of girls like this because of the yellow-green spring.
I thought it would be fun to do this.
I'd like to see a spring one.
But I'm glad I could do it too!
Please let me know you like it in the comments!
I'll be waiting for you.
Like it?